http://www.messagenet.com.au/privacy-statement

Privacy Statement
In this Statement, a reference to “MessageNet” or “us” or “we” includes MessageNet Pty Ltd ABN 97 082 712 589 and its current and future related bodies corporate and affiliates. “You” or “your” refer to the person or persons giving this consent. Please read the following information carefully and thoroughly, and if you agree to these terms and conditions, please confirm your agreement by completing the relevant fields of this form (“Form”) and clicking on “Submit”.
By completing this Form you are providing personal information (including your name, address, telephone number, bank account details, credit card information, and financial information) to MessageNet. We collect your personal information to fulfil our role as your service provider including communicating with you in relation to our products, services and events. We also collect and use your personal information to assess your creditworthiness, or provide you with credit under any application by you for commercial credit. Without your personal information we will not be able to process this Form and may not be able to provide our products and services to you.
Except as set out in this Collection Statement, the information you provide to us by completing this Form will not be disclosed to anyone else.
Our privacy policy contains information about how you may access your personal information and seek correction of such information; as well as how to complain about a breach of the Australian Privacy Principles and how we will deal with such a complaint.
Personal information collected, used or stored by MessageNet will be treated in accordance with our privacy policy, a copy of which is available at this link.
